<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>南山区免疫规划</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 南山区免疫规划</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>hugo-simpledoc-theme</title>
      <link>/hugo-simpledoc-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 00:57:40 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo-simpledoc-theme/</guid>
      <description>Hugo Simpledoc Theme is a simple and clean documentation theme for Hugo. Also you may use it for building a FAQ-page or generating an online book (why not?). This theme is a very-slightly-modified Hugo port of great WPThemeDoc.
Screenshot Features Original  Clean design
 One page
 Responsive
 Easely customizable
  Added  Hugo!
  Demo You see it in action here and now!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 00:57:40 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Installation  Install Hugo and create a new site.
 Install hugo simpledoc theme. Inside your new Hugo project run:
$ cd themes $ git clone https://github.com/aerohub/hugo-simpledoc-theme   Then take a look inside the exampleSite folder of this theme. You&amp;rsquo;ll find a file called config.toml and a folder archetypes. Copy them into the root folder of your Hugo site.
Configuration Open just-copied config.toml and fill it with your data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing Documentation</title>
      <link>/writing-documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 00:57:40 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/writing-documentation/</guid>
      <description>OK, all you need is just write!
Run in the root of your project:
hugo new my-first-doc-item.md  Then open the file with your favorite text editor and you will see something like this:
--- title: &amp;quot;My First Doc Item&amp;quot; date: 2017-12-12T00:57:40+03:00 anchor: &amp;quot;my-first-doc-item&amp;quot; weight: ---  Write your doc chapter and give it a weight. You may organize your content as you like (even with folders) but All the docs are ranged by weight here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serving and Building</title>
      <link>/serving-and-building/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 00:57:40 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/serving-and-building/</guid>
      <description>Test your site In order to see your site in action, run Hugo&amp;rsquo;s built-in local server.
$ hugo server -w  Now enter localhost:1313 in the address bar of your browser.
Build your site Just run
$ hugo  You&amp;rsquo;ll find your documentation files in public folder in the root of Hugo project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Credits and Thanks</title>
      <link>/credits-thanks-and-license/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 00:57:40 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/credits-thanks-and-license/</guid>
      <description>Many thanks go to:
 spf13 &amp;amp; Hugo
 Rich Tabor &amp;amp; original WPThemeDoc
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 01:01:13 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/license/</guid>
      <description>The MIT License (MIT)
Copyright &amp;copy; 2017 Pavel Kanyshev
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of
this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;laquo;Software&amp;raquo;), to deal in
the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to
use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of
the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>预防接种工作规范</title>
      <link>/post/guifan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/guifan/</guid>
      <description>预防接种工作规范（2016版） [TOC]
第一章 组织机构、人员及职责 1 组织机构 1.1 疾控机构 县级及以上各级疾病预防控制机构（疾控机构）设立负责预防接种工作的业务部门（中心、所、科、室）。
1.2 乡（镇）卫生院、社区卫生服务中心 乡（镇）卫生院、社区卫生服务中心依据其职责设立预防接种科室。
1.3 ==接种单位== 1.3.1 从事预防接种工作的医疗卫生机构（以下简称接种单位），由县级卫生计生行政部门指定，并明确其责任区域或任务。
1.3.2 接种单位应当具备下列条件：
1.3.2.1 具有医疗机构执业许可证件；
1.3.2.2 具有经过县级卫生计生行政部门组织的预防接种专业培训并考核合格的执业医师、执业助理医师、护士或者乡村医生；
1.3.2.3 具有符合疫苗储存、运输管理规范的冷藏设施、设备和冷藏保管制度。
1.3.2.4 乡（镇）卫生院、社区卫生服务中心及其他承担常规接种服务的城镇医疗卫生机构应当设立预防接种门诊。
2 人员 2.1 各级疾控机构、乡（镇）卫生院、社区卫生服务中心、接种单位根据其职责、任务，结合本行政区域的服务人口、服务面积和地理条件等因素，合理配置专业技术和接种人员。
2.2 承担预防接种的人员应当具备执业医师、执业助理医师、护士或者乡村医生资格，并经过县级卫生计生行政部门组织的预防接种专业培训，考核合格后方可从事预防接种服务工作。
3 职责 3.1 疾控机构 3.1.1 中国疾病预防控制中心
3.1.1.1 协助国家卫生计生委制定预防接种工作规范、国家免疫规划疫苗免疫程序和其他疫苗的使用指导原则；制定国家免疫规划相关的方案、指南等技术文件。3.1.1.2 开展预防接种相关的政策、策略和技术措施的科学研究与评估，为国家预防接种政策制定提供技术支持。
3.1.1.3 开展预防接种科普知识的宣传教育和工作人员技术培训。
3.1.1.4 开展相关疾病监测，指导疫苗可预防疾病疫情的调查处理。
3.1.1.5 开展预防接种服务技术指导与评价，承担国家免疫规划信息管理系统运行和维护，开展常规免疫接种率监测与评价。
3.1.1.6 开展预防接种异常反应监测，对地方疑似预防接种异常反应调查诊断与处理等提供技术支持。
3.1.2 省（自治区、直辖市）级疾控机构
3.1.2.1协助省级卫生计生行政部门制定本辖区国家免疫规划的实施方案、预防接种方案和相关经费预算。
3.1.2.2 制定免疫规划和预防接种相关技术方案，开展免疫规划实施和预防接种服务的督导、考核和评价工作。
3.1.2.3 拟定辖区第一类疫苗使用计划，负责第一类疫苗的分发和使用管理，组织第二类疫苗的集中采购。
3.1.2.4协助省级卫生计生行政部门制定冷链设备装备、更新计划，指导辖区冷链设备管理和温度监测。
3.1.2.5 负责国家免疫规划疫苗常规免疫接种率、第二类疫苗接种情况和人群免疫水平监测。
3.1.2.6 组织开展预防接种异常反应监测和重大疑似预防接种异常反应的调查诊断工作，协助省级卫生计生行政部门开展预防接种相关重大事件的调查处理。
3.1.2.7 组织开展疫苗可预防疾病的监测、调查和疫情控制。
3.1.2.8 负责辖区免疫规划信息管理系统维护和使用管理，收集、汇总、分析、上报免疫规划相关基础信息。
3.1.2.9 组织开展预防接种健康教育和人员培训工作。
3.1.2.10 开展预防接种相关业务的调查研究。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>